RUSSIA'S WAR - BLOOD UPON THE SNOW

THE FALL OF THE SWASTIKA
Germany is now on the brink of defeat. As the Red Army approaches Berlin, Hitler mobilizes both young and old to defend the doomed city. With the fall of Berlin and the death of his old enemy, Stalin turns once again to the control of his own people.

THE CULT OF PERSONALITY
Stalin is praised by his people for the victory he alone claims. As old age creeps up on him, Stalin's obsessive paranoia continues the persecution of his people. His plans for territorial expansion are blocked by the threat of the atomic bomb. The Cold War prevails. In 1953, Stalin dies.

B3527 • 120 MINUTES • COLOR B&W

1995 IBP Films Distribution Ltd. All Rights Reserved. Artwork 1997 Turner Home Entertainment, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
PBS and the PBS Home Video logo are registered trade and service marks of the Public Broadcasting Service.
Distributed by Warner Home Video as authorized agent for Turner Home Entertainment, Inc.
Warner Home Video, a division of Time Warner Entertainment Company, L.P.,
4000 Warner Boulevard, Burbank, California 91522.

TURNER HOME ENTERTAINMENT  PBS HOME VIDEO
PBS HOME VIDEO  ISBN: 0-7806-1882-3
