RUSSIA'S WAR - BLOOD UPON THE SNOW

THE FIGHT FROM WITHIN
During the war in the occupied Soviet Union, many oppressed Soviet citizens welcome Hitler, but their enthusiasm is short-lived as his plans are revealed. The Partisan resistance begins without Stalin's support. Then, as he begins to accept the Partisans, he provides them with supplies.

THE CAULDRON BOILS
The Wehrmacht thrusts south towards the oil fields of the Caucasus. On pain of death, Stalin specifically prohibits any retreat on the battlefield. The formation of the infamous Penal Battalions starts and the battle for Stalingrad begins.

B3525 • 120 MINUTES • COLOR / B&W

1995 IBP Films Distribution Ltd. All Rights Reserved. Artwork 1997 Turner Home Entertainment, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
PBS and the PBS Home Video logo are registered trade and service marks of the Public Broadcasting Service.
Distributed by Warner Home Video as authorized agent for Turner Home Entertainment, Inc.
Warner Home Video, a division of Time Warner Entertainment Company, L.P., 
4000 Warner Boulevard, Burbank, California 91522.

TURNER HOME ENTERTAINMENT  PBS HOME VIDEO
PBS HOME VIDEO  ISBN: 0-7806-1880-7
