RUSSIA'S WAR - BLOOD UPON THE SNOW

THE CITADEL
During the spring stalemate, all eyes turn to Kursk. Soviet war production, now moved out of the reach of German bombers, increases dramatically. The Germans prepare to meet the Red Army on the plains of Kursk. This is the greatest tank battle in the history of warfare.

FALSE DAWN
1944 is the year of victories. After a 900-day siege, Leningrad is finally liberated. The Red Army pushes westward and begins to retake the territories occupied by the Germans for so long. Once again, Stalin has plans for the people who suffer under the occupation.

B3526 • 120 MINUTES • COLOR / B&W

1995 IBP Films Distribution Ltd. All Rights Reserved. Artwork 1997 Turner Home Entertainment, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
PBS and the PBS Home Video logo are registered trade and service marks of the Public Broadcasting Service.
Distributed by Warner Home Video as authorized agent for Turner Home Entertainment, Inc.
Warner Home Video, a division of Time Warner Entertainment Company, L.P.,
4000 Warner Boulevard, Burbank, California 91522.

TURNER HOME ENTERTAINMENT  PBS HOME VIDEO
PBS HOME VIDEO  ISBN: 0-7806-1881-5
