RUSSIA'S WAR - BLOOD UPON THE SNOW

THE DARKNESS DESCENDS 
Lenin dies and leaves behind a power struggle for the leadership of the Soviet empire. He also leaves a testament-a fatal warning against Stalin's ambition. Nevertheless, Stalin rises to power and begins his war against the Soviet people: an assault on the peasantry and mysterious assassination of political rivals, and on the eve of the war with Germany, his disastrous purge of the Red Army.

THE HOUR BEFORE MIDNIGHT
Hitler becomes ever more aggressive. In Spain, Fascism and Communism face each other for the first time, while the purges in the Soviet Union reach a crescendo. In foreign affairs, Stalin plans the most astounding about-face of the century. Hitler and Stalin become allies, leading to the invasion and partition of Poland.

B3523 • 120 MINUTES • COLOR / B&W

1995 IBP Films Distribution Ltd. All Rights Reserved. Artwork 1997 Turner Home Entertainment, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
PBS and the PBS Home Video logo are registered trade and service marks of the Public Broadcasting Service.
Distributed by Warner Home Video as authorized agent for Turner Home Entertainment, Inc.
Warner Home Video, a division of Time Warner Entertainment Company, L.P.,
4000 Warner Boulevard, Burbank, California 91522.

TURNER HOME ENTERTAINMENT  PBS HOME VIDEO
PBS HOME VIDEO  ISBN: 0-7806-1878-5
