RUSSIA'S WAR - BLOOD UPON THE SNOW

THE GOTHS RIDE EAST 
The Germans invade the Soviet Union, leading to chaos and confusion as the Red Army falls back. Stalin, paralyzed by the shock, retreats to his dacha. Minsk, Kiev and Smolensk fall. Stalin returns from hiding and signs the infamous Order 270, branding captured Soviet officers as traitors and committing their wives to forced labor. With the first snows, the Wehrmacht arrives at the gates of Moscow.

BETWEEN LIFE AND DEATH
The Germans are at the gates of Moscow. The winter closes in and starvation claims thousands of lives in the besieged city of Leningrad. The Red Army counterattacks on the Moscow front.

B3524 • 120 MINUTES • COLOR / B&W

1995 IBP Films Distribution Ltd. All Rights Reserved. Artwork 1997 Turner Home Entertainment, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
PBS and the PBS Home Video logo are registered trade and service marks of the Public Broadcasting Service.
Distributed by Warner Home Video as authorized agent for Tuner Home Entertainment, Inc.
Warner Home Video, a division of Time Warner Entertainment Company, L.P.,
4000 Warner Boulevard, Burbank, California 91522.

TURNER HOME ENTERTAINMENT  PBS HOME VIDEO
PBS HOME VIDEO  ISBN: 0-7806-1879-3